https://www.plastic-cards.com.au/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
Our organization is committed to the protection of your personal information.Custom Plastic Cards will not reveal, disclose, sell, distribute, rent, license, share or pass your personal information on to any third parties without your explicit written consent via email, facsimile or mail. In all cases, your information will be held in strict confidence. The Custom Plastic Cards web site has no facility to automatically recognize information regarding the visitor's domain or email address whilst the visitor is browsing and not deliberately submitting information.Custom Plastic Cards will not collect any personal information from you revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, details of health, disability or sexual activity or orientation. Exceptions to this include:* Where you have given express consent to Custom Plastic Cards to do so* Where there are reasonable grounds to believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health* Where the use is authorized by law or reasonably necessary to enforce the law or when the information is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claimCustom Plastic Cards may only use your personal information or data for the purpose of responding to your communication, giving support or help related to our product/s, checking the status of the usage of our product/s and direct marketing in relation to promotional activities. Again, your details will not be given to a third party without your consent as described above. You may also notify us at any time if you would like us to destroy your personal information or if you do not wish to receive any further communication from Custom Plastic Cards. To do either of the latter two activities go to our Contact Us page (http://www.martialartssoftware.com/order.htm), express your option and include your name and email address.If you have any concerns or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us toll free at 1 300 651 544 or emailsecurity@plastic-cards.com.au
or use the Contact Us page.
